The American Red Cross on Naval Station Guantanamo Bay held
a hurricane preparedness event featuring base organizations such as Fleet
and Family, the fire department, and security, who provided information
on tropical weather emergencies.
The important reason why we have this preparedness event is
to make sure our community is resilient and can respond
and recover from disasters that happen.
We want to make sure that their families are prepared if
they have to evacuate or if they have to go
into shelters.
Naval Station Guantanamo Bay is in a very unique
position.
We are in the path of many of the hurricanes
that come through.
So we need to be prepared in order to meet
those challenges that those hurricanes bring.
Reporting from AFN Guantanamo Bay, I'm Petty Officer Zach Guth.